const QUIZ = [
  {
    question: 'At what skill level can you start training for a marathon?',
    answers: ['Olympic athelete', 'Any', 'Experienced runner of many years', 'Beginner to running'],
    correctAnswer: 'Any',
    answerExplaination: 'Training begins with a plan, and planning can start at any skill level.'
    },
  {
    question: 'How long is a marathon?',
    answers: ['26.2 miles', '13.1 miles', '40 miles', '10 miles'],
    correctAnswer: '26.2 miles',
    answerExplaination:'While originally about 40 kilometers, in 1921 the length for a marathon was formally standardized at 26.2 miles.'
    },
  {
    question: 'During training, after how many weeks of progressively longer runs should you take an "easy" week?',
    answers: ['3-4', '5-6', '2', 'Never'],
    correctAnswer: '3-4',
    answerExplaination:"An 'easy' or 'rest' week every 3-4 weeks gives your body time to rebuild."
    },
  {
    question: 'How long should you be able to run without stopping or walking before starting a marathon program?',
    answers: ['30 mins', '60 mins', '120 mins', '180 mins'],
    correctAnswer: '30 mins',
    answerExplaination:"Running for 30 minutes is all that's required to start your training.  The first step is getting to 30 minutes."
    },
  {
    question: 'In marathon training, how many long runs are there per week?',
    answers: ['1', '2', '5', '6'],
    correctAnswer: '1',
    answerExplaination:'While long runs are essential, more than 1 a week does not give your body time to rebuild.'
    },
  {
    question: 'In marathon training, what is the minimum number of runs per week?',
    answers: ['3', '4', '5', '7'],
    correctAnswer: '3',
    answerExplaination:'Training plans vary widely, but 3 runs per week should be the minimum for any marathon training plan.'
    },
  {
    question: 'How long is a typical marathon training program?',
    answers: ['12-16 weeks', '16-20 weeks', '8 weeks', '20+ weeks'],
    correctAnswer: '12-16 weeks',
    answerExplaination:"Beginner plans may be longer, and advanced plans shorter, but the typical training plan is 12-16 weeks."
    },
  {
    question: 'What is the most common mistake with beginners to marathon training?',
    answers: ['Run too fast', 'Run too slow', 'Buy too many shoes', 'Don\'t match outfit to shoes'],
    correctAnswer: 'Run too fast',
    answerExplaination:"Marathons are about endurance first, and speed second.  Start slow and build up."
    },
  {
    question: 'What is the best footwear for marathon training?',
    answers: ['Name brand running shoe with full arch support and orthodics (if necessary)', 'Minimalist shoe with little to no support', 'Barefoot', 'All the above'],
    correctAnswer: 'All the above',
    answerExplaination:"Every runner is different.  Find what works best for you."
    },
  {
    question: 'What is the only designation a marathoner should be ashamed of?',
    answers: ['Second place (the first one to lose)', 'Finished in last place', 'DNF (did not finish)', 'DNS (did not start)'],
    correctAnswer: 'DNS (did not start)',
    answerExplaination:"The hardest part is getting yourself to the start line.  It requires planning, training, and resolve."
    }
];
